vapesocietysupply.com 2016-08-31

# Privacy Policy – Vape Society Supply

## **EMAIL INFORMATION**

Please do not provide sensitive personal information to us by e-mail. Instead, use our web forms, which employ SSL technology (see “How do we protect you and your information”). However, if you choose to correspond with us via email, we will retain the content of your email message together with your email address and our responses. We use administrative, technical and physical security measures to protect our computing infrastructure and your personal information from unauthorized use, access, modification or disclosure.

## **How do we protect visitor information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.

## **WEBSITES LINKED TO VapeSocietySupply.COM**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our website nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.

## **PRIVACY OF CHILDREN**

Children under the age of 18 are not allowed to use our web site and/or products. If you are under the age of 18, you can use this service only in conjunction with permission from your parents or legal guardians.

## **CONTACT US**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, our website VapeSocietySupply.com, or your order with us, please contact us.

## **NOTICE**

VapeSocietySupply.com reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time by direct electronic notification to you or by posting the amended terms on this page. All amended terms shall automatically be effective for new users or new purchases immediately on posting and, in all other cases, 30 days after they are initially posted and dated, unless otherwise specified in a notice to you.

Questions? Visit Our [Contact Us](http://www.vapesocietysupply.com/pages/contact-us "Contact Us") Page!

WARNING: Our products contain nicotine, a poisonous and addictive substance. Our products are only intended for committed smokers of legal smoking age and not by non-smokers, children, women who are pregnant or may become pregnant or any person with an elevated risk of, or preexisting condition of, any medical condition which includes, but is not limited to, heart disease, diabetes, high blood pressure or asthma. If you experience any side effects or possible side effects, stop using the product immediately and consult a physician. Product may be poisonous if orally ingested. Our products are not smoking cessation products and have not been tested or guaranteed as such. Our products have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration nor is it intended to treat, prevent or cure any disease or condition. For their protection, please keep out of reach of children and pets. Read our terms of use page before purchasing our products.
